Jerome Kern Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Show Music (Box 1-95, Box 103-116)
  - Manuscripts (Box 1-94, Box 103-116)
    - Very Warm for May (1939) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - Night club finale (vocal), Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 13 p. (Box-folder 112/8)
      - Night club finale: new #15, Parts (Box-folder 85/3)
      - Segue. Finale-night-club: new #15a, Parts; Uniform title: Night club finale (Box-folder 85/4)
      - Night club insert, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal scores (3) in ink, no lyric; [2] p. (Box-folder 79/1)
      - North-South incidental, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 7 p. (Box-folder 112/9)
      - North-South incidental: #10, Parts (Box-folder 85/5)
      - North-South incid.: #11, Parts (Box-folder 85/6)
      - North-South incid.: new #28, Parts (Box-folder 85/7)
      - Ogdon's characterization, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 39 p. (Box-folder 112/10)
      - Ogdon's characterization, Ozalids (3) of ms. piano-vocal score, variant annotations in pencil; 18 p. (Box-folder 79/2)
      - Ogdon's characterization: choral parts, Ozalids (6) of ms. choral scores (SATB), variant annotations in pencil; 3 p.; Note: lyric fragments in pencil on backs and lyric sheets (2) laid in, mostly of other songs (Box-folder 79/3)
      - Ogdon's characterization: #7, Parts (Box-folder 85/8)
      - Opening act II: part I; New curtain rise act II; Old opening act II, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 13 p. + p. 9-13 (Box-folder 112/11)
      - Opening act II: part I: new #16b, Parts (Box-folder 85/9)
      - Opening act II: part I: old #16b, Parts (Box-folder 86/1)
      - Opening act II: part II: #17 See also: "Musket", Parts (Box-folder 86/2)
      - Opening act II: no. 1 See also: "Melody in F" in Series II -- Miscellaneous Music, Ozalid of ms. piano-vocal score, annotations in red pencil, no lyric; 3 p. (Box-folder 79/4)
      - [Opening act II]: The cricket: there's something about a musket, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, annotations in pencil, no lyric; 1 p.; On back: 2-measure sketch in pencil (Box-folder 79/4)
      - Opening act II: Parker Daniels: no. 31 See also: "Whippoorwill" in Series II -- Miscellaneous Music, Ozalid of ms. piano-vocal score, annotations in Kern's hand in red pencil, no lyric; 3 p. (Box-folder 79/5)
      - Opening act II -- quartet, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal scores (2) in ink, no lyric; [2] p. and [3] p.; Note: pencil sketch on back of 2 p. ms. (Box-folder 79/6)
      - Vocal opening act II, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) choral score in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 79/6)
      - Opening act II (voices), Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) choral score in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 79/6)
      - Opening scene III, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 20 p. (Box-folder 112/12)
      - Opening scene III act I, Ozalids (2) of ms. piano-score; 5 p. (Box-folder 79/7)
      - Opening scene III: #5, Parts (Box-folder 86/3)
      - Overture, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 46 p. (Box-folder 112/13)
      - Overture, Parts (Box-folder 86/4)
      - [Pale moonbeams]: Melos before music in my heart See also: "Grazioso in D" in Series II -- Miscellaneous Music See also: Finale ultimo b See also: Finale ultimo g, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; [4] p. (Box-folder 79/8)
      - Play-out, Parts (Box-folder 86/5)
      - Prelude act I, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 22 p. (Box-folder 113/1)
      - Prelude act I, Ozalids (3) of ms. piano/piano-vocal score, variant annotations in pencil; 13 p.; Note: includes "Me and the roll and you" (Box-folder 79/9)
      - Prelude act I, Parts (Box-folder 86/6)
      - Quartet, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 11 p. (Box-folder 113/2)
      - Quartet, Ms. vocal parts (SSAT) in ink or pencil; [4] p.; Ozalids (2) of ms. piano-vocal score (SATB), 1 copy with annotations in pencil; 6 p. (Box-folder 79/10)
      - [Quartet], Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 6 p. (Box-folder 79/10)
      - Quartet: #8, Parts (Box-folder 87/1)
      - Raymond to Patsy: later Patsy to Sonny See also: "No. 6" in Series II -- Miscellaneous Music, Ozalid of ms. piano-vocal score, no lyric; 8 p. (Box-folder 79/11)
      - Rhumba opening #1: act II, Ozalid of ms. piano-vocal score, annotations in pencil, no lyric; 5 p. (Box-folder 79/12)
      - Opening act II cont.: curtain prelude built on musket: no. 33, Ozalid of ms. piano-vocal score, annotations in pencil, no lyric; 5 p. (Box-folder 79/12)
      - Rhumba, Ms. piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [6] p. (Box-folder 79/12)
      - Rhumba opening #2: act II See also: Mister man in Series II -- Miscellaneous Music, Ozalid of ms. piano-vocal score, no lyric; 4 p.; Photocopy and negative of the above; Note: some dummy lyrics by Kern (Box-folder 79/12)
      - Sally dances, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in pencil and ink; 32 p. (Box-folder 113/3)
      - Sally dance interlude: segue Harlem, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, lyric in pencil; 11 p. (Box-folder 79/13)
      - Sally dances: #27b, Parts (Box-folder 87/2)
      - Scene change: montage into final set: #29, Ms. full score in ink; 21 p. (Box-folder 113/4)
      - Scene change: montage into final set: no. 17, Ozalids (2) of ms. piano-vocal score, variant annotations in pencil, 1 copy includes lyric; 5 p.; Note: 1 copy titled "State police" (Box-folder 79/14)
      - Scene change: #29, Parts (Box-folder 87/3)
      - Serpentine: #16a, #15b See also: "Heaven in my arms" (full score), Parts (Box-folder 87/4)
      - Soft shoe dance, Ms. full score in ink; 9 p. (Box-folder 113/5)
      - [That] lucky fellow, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 56 p. (Box-folder 113/6)
      - Change music: #21a, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 1 p. (Box-folder 113/6)
      - That lucky fellow, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil; 6 p. (Box-folder 79/15)
      - That lucky fellow, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, annotations in pencil, no lyric; [5] p.; Ozalids (2) of ms. piano-vocal scores, variant annotations in pencil; 15 p. (Box-folder 79/15)
      - That lucky fellow, Printed piano-vocal scores (2); 5 p. (Box-folder 79/15)
      - [That] lucky fellow: #18 See also: "Finale ultimo f", Parts (Box-folder 87/5)
      - [That] lucky lady, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 26 p. (Box-folder 113/7)
      - [That] lucky lady: #20, Parts (Box-folder 87/6)
      - There's something about a musket see: Musket
      - Uncommercial traveller: no. 36 See also: "#36 Parker & Daniels" in Series II -- Miscellaneous Music, Ozalid of ms. piano-vocal score, annotations in pencil, no lyric; 5 p.; Note: title partially erased (Box-folder 79/16)
      - W. Long routine: op. act II: #16c, Parts (Box-folder 88/1)
      - Winnie's reprise: #16, Parts (Box-folder 88/2)
      - [Unidentified]: #4a (change), Parts (Box-folder 88/3)
      - [Unidentified]: no. 6, Parts (Box-folder 88/4)
      - [Unidentified]: #6a, Parts (Box-folder 88/5)
      - [Unidentified]: #15 df, Parts (Box-folder 88/6)
      - [Unidentified]: #22 change, Parts (Box-folder 88/7)
      - [Unidentified]: 22 a and 23, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink and pencil; 14 p. (Box-folder 113/10)
      - [Unidentified]: #22 a & 23, Parts (Box-folder 88/8)
      - [Unidentified]: #24, Parts (Box-folder 88/9)
      - [Unidentified]: #25a, Parts (Box-folder 88/10)
      - [Unidentified]: no. 26, Parts (Box-folder 89/1)
      - [Unidentified]: new #27, Parts (Box-folder 89/2)
      - [Unidentified]: introduction to #27, Parts (Box-folder 89/3)
      - [Unidentified]: new #27b, Parts (Box-folder 89/4)
      - [Unidentified]: #26a, #27b, Parts (Box-folder 89/5)
      - [Unidentified]: new #29, Parts (Box-folder 89/6)
      - [Unidentified]: #29 very new, Parts (Box-folder 89/7)
      - [Bobby Dolan's orchestration sketches], Ms. (various hands, including Robert Russell Bennett) outlines of musical routines, song listings, piano scores, sketches, lead sheets, short scores, notes in pencil and ink; Includes, but is not limited to music for: "Ballet finale act II" "Boogie woogie" "Brain ballet" "L'histoire de Madame de la Tour" "Music in my heart" "Night club finale" "Quartet" "Rhumba opening" "[That] lucky fellow" (Box-folder 90/1)
      - Very Warm for May, Typed scripts (2) for radio play version; 18 p. (p. 3 missing from 1 copy); Note: broadcast on June 4, 1951; Laid in: Typed letter; [1] p. Note: letter to Mr. Edgar Carver of Rodgers & Hammerstein from Genevieve Fisch of Benton & Bowles, Inc. advertising agency (Box-folder 90/2)
      - [Serial]: Local 802 A. F. of M. Official Journal, New York, January 1940. Periodical; 31 p. (Box-folder 90/3)
    - You Were Never Lovelier
      - [Various titles] see: Series II -- Miscellaneous Music
    - Ziegfeld Follies of 1916
      - My lady of the Nile, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink, lyric in ink and pencil; [4] p.; Lyric by Gene Buck (Box-folder 90/4)
      - My lady of the Nile, Parts (arrangement by Charles Miller) (Box-folder 90/5)
    - Zip Goes a Million (1919) lyrics by Buddy DeSylva
      - Bill, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 9 p. (Box-folder 91/1)
      - Bill, Parts (Box-folder 92/4)
      - A business of our own, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 26 p. (Box-folder 91/2)
      - A business of our own, Parts (Box-folder 92/5)
      - Finale act I, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 45 p. (Box-folder 91/3)
      - Finale act I, Parts (Box-folder 92/6)
      - Finale act II, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 30 p. (Box-folder 91/4)
      - Finale act 2nd [sic], Parts (Box-folder 92/7)
      - Finale ultimo, Parts (Box-folder 92/8)
      - Forget-me-not, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 20 p. (Box-folder 91/5)
      - Forget me not, Parts (Box-folder 92/9)
      - Give a thought to Broadway, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 14 p. (Box-folder 91/6)
      - Give a thought to Broadway, Parts (Box-folder 92/10)
      - Hail! and speech, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 14 p.; Note: a.k.a. "Monty's speech" (Box-folder 91/7)
      - Hail! and speech, Parts (Box-folder 92/11)
      - Incidental, Parts (Box-folder 93/1)
      - It's better to be a man, Arranger's holograph (Maurice B. de Packh) full score in ink; 15 p. (Box-folder 91/8)
      - It's better to be a man, Parts (Box-folder 93/2)
      - The language of love, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 31 p. (Box-folder 91/9)
      - The language of love See also: "Genevieve and men" from Dear Sir, Printed piano-vocal score, annotations in pencil; 7 p.; Note: "Genevieve & men act II" written on cover (Box-folder 92/1)
      - The language of love, Parts (Box-folder 93/3)
      - The little back yard band, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 34 p. (Box-folder 91/10)
      - The little back yard band, Parts (Box-folder 93/4)
      - Look for the silver lining See also: Sally, Parts (Box-folder 93/5)
      - A man around the house, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 22 p. (Box-folder 91/11)
      - A man around the house, Parts (Box-folder 93/6)
      - The mandolin and the man, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 92/2)
      - The mandolin [and the man], Parts (Box-folder 93/7)
      - Opening act II, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 22 p. (Box-folder 91/12)
      - Opening act II, Parts (Box-folder 93/8)
      - Opening act III, Arranger's holograph (Maurice B. de Packh) full score in ink; 24 p. (Box-folder 91/13)
      - Opening act III, Parts (Box-folder 93/9)
      - Overture, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 20 p.; Includes: "The language of love" "A man around the house" "Whippoorwill" "The mandolin and the man" (Box-folder 91/14)
      - Overture, Parts (Box-folder 94/1)
      - Producers, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 22 p. (Box-folder 91/15)
      - Producers, Parts (Box-folder 94/2)
      - Smile: opening act I, Parts (Box-folder 94/3)
      - Smiles, Parts (Box-folder 94/4)
      - Telephone girls, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 17 p. (Box-folder 91/16)
      - Telephone girls, Parts; Note: also listed as "Opening act II after Entr'acte -- You tell 'em" (Box-folder 94/5)
      - Whippoorwill See also: "Whip-poor-will" from Sally, Parts (Box-folder 94/6)
      - You tell 'em, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 21 p. (Box-folder 91/17)
      - You tell 'em, Parts (Box-folder 94/7)
      - [Lyric sheets], Typed lyric sheets (asterisked titles include a ms. lyric sheet in pencil, possibly in Buddy DeSylva's hand, on Jerome Kern stationary); [43] p.; Includes: Back yard band Bill A business of our own Finale act one *Finale act two Forget-me-not Give a thought to Broadway [Hail! and speech]: Monty's speech *It's better to be a man The language of love A man around the house The mandolin and the man *Opening act two Opening chorus act one Producers Something must be the matter with me Telephone girls Whippoorwill You tell 'em (Box-folder 92/3)
  - Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music (Box 95)
    - Calliope: Mitzi's ch[orus], Ms. lead sheet in ink, annotations in pencil, ms. sketch in pencil on back; [2] p.; Note: probably intended for Head Over Heels (Box-folder 95/1)
    - Caprice, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 6 p.; Note: same music as "The weeping willow tree" from Dear Sir (Box-folder 95/2)
    - Cocoanut dance, Ms. lead sheet/sketch in pencil; [1] p.; Note: probably intended for Lucky (Box-folder 95/3)
    - Dance through life with you, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 12 p.; Note: this may be "Dance through life with me" written for Girls Will Be Girls (retitled Love o' Mike) and dropped during tryout (later considered for Very Good Eddie), or, "I'd love to dance through life with you" from A Modern Eve (Box-folder 95/4)
    - Do look at him: Bill, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, annotations in Kern's hand in pencil; [3] p.; Note: probably intended for Oh, Lady! Lady!! (Box-folder 95/5)
    - Don't forget: duet (Stella and Ted), Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; [4] p.; Note: probably intended for Love o' Mike (Box-folder 95/6)
    - Entrance of girls, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 5 p.; Note: written for She's a Good Fellow, reused in Sunny (Box-folder 95/7)
    - Finale act I, Ms. piano score in pencil, annotations in Kern's hand in ink; [1] p.; Note: probably intended for Lucky (Box-folder 95/8)
    - Finaletto act I, Ms. piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; [9] p.; Note: probably intended for Very Good Eddie, but unused (Box-folder 95/9)
    - Finaletto act I, Holograph sketch in pencil; 5 p.; Note: probably intended for Dear Sir (Box-folder 95/10)
    - Garden of girls, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano score in ink; [2] p.; Note: same music as "Package of seeds"; written for Oh, Boy! (Box-folder 95/11)
    - God rest you merry gentlemen: christmas carol, Ms. piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Note on t.p.: "arranged as a modern 'Blues' by Jerome Kern" (Box-folder 95/12)
    - God rest you merry gentlemen: christmas carol, Printed piano-vocal score [non-Kern arrangement]; p. 10 (Box-folder 95/12)
    - A great idea, Ms. piano-vocal score in pencil; 3 p. (Box-folder 95/13)
    - Human after all, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 16 p.; Note: probably intended for Love o' Mike (Box-folder 95/14)
    - [I have been around a bit]: Duet: Madge -- Jerry, Ms. full score in ink; 18 p.; Note: probably intended for Ninety in the Shade (Box-folder 95/15)
    - If eventually, why not now, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, lyric partially in ink; [3] p.; Note: blue pencil marks in Frank Saddler's hand date piece as pre-1921 (Box-folder 95/16)
    - It's a mile and a half (to easy street), Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 3 p.; Lyric by Schuyler Greene, dated 1915 (Box-folder 95/17)
    - It's wireless, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 5 p.; Note: burthen is same music as burthen in "Little church around the corner" from Sally (Box-folder 95/18)
    - A little closer, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, typed lyric; 4 p.; Lyric by M.E. Rourke, dated 1910 (Box-folder 95/19)
    - Little Eva, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 4 p.; Note: probably from The Dairymaids (Box-folder 95/20)
    - Madrigalette: #13, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, vocal lines in Kern's hand in pencil, no lyric; 8 p. (Box-folder 95/21)
    - Me, Holograph piano score in pencil; [2] p.; Note: probably intended for Head Over Heels (Box-folder 95/22)
    - Mendocino stroll, Ms. piano-vocal score in pencil; 6 p.; Music and lyric by Donald Brian and Jerome Kern (Box-folder 95/23)
    - Minstrels, Holograph sketch in variously colored pencils; 2 p. (Box-folder 95/24)
    - Morganatic love: duet (Zaza and Atlas), Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 6 p.; Lyric by Noel Coward, music reused for Dear Sir (Box-folder 95/25)
    - My Bonnie Jean, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 8 p. (Box-folder 95/26)
    - Opening act II, Holograph lead sheet/sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 95/27)
    - Fox trot, Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 95/28)
    - Op. act II: dance, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano score in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 95/28)
    - Op. scene 2: M[itz]i, Ms. vocal arrangement/sketch in ink; [1] p. (small) (Box-folder 95/29)
    - Publicity, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 2 p.; Note on front: "Dear Frank [Saddler] This is designed for the comedian to speak the verse and sing the Burthen alone on the stage. But I think we had better have a fuller arrangement of the Burthen prepared in case they want to use the chorus. So will you please make a 1st and 2nd ending to the Burthen, which will have the wood and Brass cued in and marked 'Play 2nd time only' There is a flat box of Tomato seedlings waiting for you here. Yrs. Jerome" (Box-folder 95/30)
    - Ten nights in a ball room: blues, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score, no lyric; 7 p.; Note: probably intended for Sitting Pretty, but unused (Box-folder 95/31)
    - Terzetto (ultimo), Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 3 p.; Note: probably intended for Dear Sir (Box-folder 95/32)
    - Wedding scene, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 3 p. (incomplete); Lyric by George V. Hobart; Note: written for Polish Wedding, reused in Oh, Lady! Lady!! (Box-folder 95/33)
    - When a woman!, Arranger's holograph (Max Steiner) full score in ink; 20 p. (Box-folder 95/34)
    - [Wishing well scene], Holograph sketch in pencil; p. 2 (Box-folder 95/35)
    - [Wishing well scene], Holograph sketch in pencil; p. 6 (Box-folder 95/35)
    - [Wishing] well scene, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) sketch in pencil; [1] p.; Note: sketches appear unrelated; music used in Dear Sir and Sunny (Box-folder 95/35)
    - You and I: Song (Mac Forland), Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, lyric in Kern's hand in pencil; 8 p.; Lyric by P.G. Wodehouse, dated 1916; Mimeograph of typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 95/36)
    - [Unidentified holograph], Holograph sketch [G major in 2/4] in pencil; 1 p. (small); Note: probably intended for Dear Sir, but unused (Box-folder 95/37)
    - [Unidentified holograph], Holograph sketch [C minor in 2/4] in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 95/37)
    - [Unidentified holograph], Holograph sketch [F major in 2/2] in pencil; 2 p. (Box-folder 95/37)
    - [Unidentified manuscripts], Mss.; [24] p.; Includes: Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) sketch in pencil; p. 2. Note: probably intended for Dear Sir Ms. piano score in ink; p. 9-10 Ms. piano-vocal score in ink; p. 2-3. Note: includes markings by Frank Saddler; title may be "Wouldn't that be nice" Ms. piano-vocal score in ink; [1] p. Ms. piano score in ink; [1] p. Ms. piano score in ink; [2] p. Note: top half of p. [1] torn off Ms. piano score in ink; [1] p. Ms. sketches in ink and pencil; [1] p. Ms. piano score in ink; [1] p. Note: probably intended for Nobody Home or Oh, Boy! Ms. lead sheet/sketch in pencil; [2] p. Note: probably intended for Lucky Ms. violin part in ink, annotations in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 95/38)
    - [Lyric sheets], Typed lyric sheets; [4] p.; Includes: May bells: Rose and girls Golden rainbow [Up town -- New York]: Trio -- Guy, Mary and Patsy Song: Pat & men (Box-folder 95/39)
- Miscellaneous Music (Box 96-100)
  The Miscellaneous Music (Series II) is mostly comprised of copies of late songs by Kern. Many of these were songs that were cut from films, or written for unproduced projects. In some cases, lyrics were added to previously unused works after Kern's death. Apparently, most of this material came from the files of T. B. Harms>, Inc. (Kern's publisher) and some appear to have been transcribed from recordings made by Kern.
  Arrangement of the Miscellaneous Music (Series II) is divided into two subseries. The first subseries, Titled, is sorted alphabetically by title. The second subseries, Untitled, is arranged by folder level description.
  - Miscellaneous Music (Titled) (Box 96-99)
    - Afternoon of a siren, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 3 p. (Box-folder 96/1)
    - All's well with the world: new #32, Photocopy and negative of copyist's ms. piano-vocal score; p. 14-27; Lyric by Otto Harbach; Note: intended for Stolen Dreams/Man in the Sky; dated 6/7/30 (Box-folder 96/2)
    - April fooled me, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; [3] p.; Lyric by Dorothy Fields (Box-folder 96/3)
    - [Untitled]: C.5, Photocopy and negative of ms. piano-vocal score, no lyric; 4 p.; Note: "Sentimental song" on negative only (Box-folder 96/3)
    - Baby, Photocopy of ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score, no lyric; 3 p. (Box-folder 96/4)
    - Back in my shell: new #20 See also: "Barrelhouse beguine", Photocopy and negative of ms. piano-vocal score, no lyric; 3 p.; Note: "Serenade" on negative only; Note: from One Night in the Tropics (1940), lyric by Dorothy Fields (Box-folder 96/5)
    - Barrelhouse beguine, Ms. lead sheet in pencil, no lyric; [1] p. (Box-folder 96/6)
    - Barrelhouse beguine: new #25 See also: "Back in my shell", Photocopy of ms. piano-vocal score; 4 p.; Lyric by Johnny Mercer; Note: from You Were Never Lovelier; copyright 1942 (Box-folder 96/6)
    - Bells: new #7, Photocopy and negative of ms. piano-vocal score, no lyric; 3 p. (Box-folder 96/7)
    - Bubble ballet: new #42, Photocopy and negative of ms. piano score; 4 p. (Box-folder 96/8)
    - Buda-Pest: no. 10, Photocopies (3) and negative of ms. piano-vocal score, no lyric, annotations in pencil; 4 p.; Note: "Rhythmical song" on negative only; Note: a.k.a. "I was young in Budapest"; copyright 1938 (Box-folder 96/9)
    - Business, Photocopies (2) and negative of ms. piano-vocal score, no lyric; 5 p. (Box-folder 96/10)
    - Canzonetta: new #54, Photocopy and negative of ms. (Robert R. Bennett) piano-vocal score, no lyric; 8 p.; Lyric not present, credited to Oscar Hammerstein II; Note: intended for High, Wide and Handsome; On front: "Oscar This is merely a Jennie dear only not as good" (Box-folder 96/11)
    - Chinese lantern love, Copyist's ms. and negative photocopy of piano-vocal score, no lyric; 4 p.; Note: negative photocopy has only 2 p. (Box-folder 96/12)